I've been on this channel and on social
media for a few years trying to explain
to people that the emperor is not
wearing clothes that our governments
don't have the capacity to fix our
problems corporations don't have the
will or capacity to fix our problems in
their current state and realizing that
convincing people the Emperor isn't
wearing clothes is not the point of that
story in fact when the boy says it
everyone can see it at that moment so if
everyone can't see it in the moment you
say it it's a mute point to try to
convince people and I think the emperor
is convincing us that they are not in
fact wearing any clothing with ghovat 19
with the riots and long before the
current protests and riots there were a
lot of protests happening we have been
waking up and doing waking up to the
heard isn't wearing clothes so the other
thing I've been trying to do because
what you're supposed to do is convince
everyone somehow that I'm wearing
clothes when well it continually try to
take them off like showing my
vulnerability showing all of my weakness
while trying to say right I know it
sounds like I'm trying to be the new
emperor like I know how to save the
world I'm wearing clothes I promised
when that neither of those things is
what I'm actually trying to do nor is it
what needs to happen all it convinces
the wrong word but convincing all of the
spectators that they are wearing clothes
they are enough to save this world they
are enough to turn humanity around and I
don't need to convince them I just have
to get them to look down like you're
already wearing clothes you were already
enough exactly as you are
exactly with the knowledge you hold the
expertise you hold because you are the
expert at being you and that's all you
have to bring to the table and in so
doing I don't need to convince everybody
that they're wearing clothes just the
people who are ready to see it just the
people who are ready to look down
see that they're wearing clothes it
doesn't matter what I'm doing dance
measure the moon night naked or in a
full-on parka because it isn't about my
clothes or the Emperors it's about all
of ours that we all have the capacity to
do this everybody has an amazing purpose
and the purpose is to be you find you
find your people and be you and that is
what I am asking people to do and it's
all I can ask of myself to I can't force
everyone to see that the Emperor's not
wearing clothes I can't force them to
not try to get the Emperor new clothes
instead realize that they themselves are
wearing them they never needed an
emperor Wow we may be needed one we
don't need one anymore thank you a
better worlds on its way when we are all
gonna participate in co-creating it
together please like and subscribe